<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Stargate Races</name>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<author>Fenris</author>
	<description>This mod adds the Race of the Wraith and the Goa'uld from the Series Stargate. This mod was heavily inspired on the RimGate - Jaffa, Kree! mod and is increasing now. This one adds the Jaffa with their Armor, the Staff weapon and the Stungun but it wasn't possilbe to build them yourself. Therefore I have rewritten the Mod and add some other stuff myself, as well as I retexutred and rewrote some very interesting mods to add more flavour.
It is work in progress as it is super time consuming as it is my first mod and I should focus a bit more oin my PhD thesis - Feel free to join and help me, especially if you know C# modding ( I have no clue, I tried and it is more difficult for me)

The mod contains (v1.2):
Two new Race inculding the suitable scenario:
Goa'uld:
- The one Race is called Goa'uld, in order to choose if your pawns are Goa'uld, Jaffa or slaves you need to choose their Backstories. I recommend to play with 1 Goa'uld, 2 Jaffa and 3 Slaves.
Armor and Weapons
- Jaffa Armor with Helmets, Ma'tok (STaff Weapon) and Zat (StunGun)(all orginally from RimGate - Jaffa, Kree! by Xen, Charnov, Helixien, Cpt. Ohu and Erdelf)
- golden Goa'uld Armor and Helemts
- Kull Armor and weapon
- Tacluchnatagamuntoron (grenade)
- Tel'tak transport ship, which brings you where every you want and back (orginially it was Cargo Pod Transport by AKreedz)
- Mineable Naqadah which can be refined to Naqadriah at the Electric Smelter (inspired by Coal from Agrarcore) 
- Naqadriah Power Generator
- The sarcophagus (inspired by Fast regen by Daniledman)
- the necessary research table

Wraith:
- They are carnivore and need a lot of meat. Build a cocoon as fast as possible. (inspired from MeatLab-Mod)
- Meat can be transfered to Biomass at the butcher table
- Biomass is a necessary ressource
- They have their own meat based power source
- They have a stun gun (which unfortuenaltey is ugly) and their own grandes (for killing people)
- Hair is from Lord of the Rim-Eleven mod as well as vanilla game
- Icon is from https://www.kisspng.com/png-teyla-emmagan-wraith-stargate-symbol-royal-seal-3377928/download-png.html
- Due to my lack of C# modding I cannot give them a working Shuttle, somehow the assemblies is just allowed one kind of shuttle

I want to add a StarGate which would count as Wincondition, but I simple don't know how^^

If you want to use this mod as basis for your own versions of any other stargate race (replicants, ancient, wraith) or as basis for a mediveal king, knight and slave scenario feel free to use it. Remember to mention all other autohors. 

I recommend to play it with one of the many Shield mods to enable more sci-fi feeling (e.g. ED-ShieldsBasic)

P.s. I couldn't fix that the pawn in the sarcophagus doesn't show its stupid head. I would be happy for a fix. 

v.1.1
Due to some problems I have created a Goa'uld and a Wraith Crafting Table where their stuff can be crafted. So no data are overrided of the original files. THis should help to work with different mods too. Unfortunetla I couldn't fix any head issues as the files are all properly labelled. It should work, but I am not a good coder nor artist (as you might realise^^).
v.1.2
Thanks to EbonJaeger the game is now balanced and a lot of string errors are fixed. Finally I found the reason why the benches didn't work and it is fixed now too.

</description>
</ModMetaData>